

DMITRY SHAVLUKEVICH

FRONT-END DEVELOPER (REACT)

SKILLS

React/Redux JavaScript/TypeScript Axios/REST API MongoDB/ SQL Git/Github Material-UI/PrimeVue Vue/Vuex

ENGLISH

Less/Sass

NodeJS/Express

Pre-Intermediate (in progress)

EDUCATION

IT-INCUBATOR, 2021-2022

Front-end developer (React/ Redux/ Typescript/ JS/ES6+)

BELARUSIAN NATIONAL TECHNICAL **UNIVERSITY, 2019**

Bachelor degree in electrical engineering

CONTACTS



+375 29 582 91 59











sh.dg.msq@mail.ru

Minsk. Belarus

ABOUT ME

I'm a JavaScript developer with experience building landing pages and single page apps using React (JS/TS), Redux, and maintaining and developing rich projects (MEVN).

Now I am improving my skills in these areas and expanding them with new technologies, and in my free time I devote to solving the CodeWars kata and improving my English.

At the moment, I would like to find a project/full-time job in a creative company with an urgent task and a close-knit team!

WORK EXPERIENCE

CJSC ADVIN SMART FACTORY, 2022 - present time

JAVASCRIPT ENGINEER (MEVN)

- Supporting of existing functional;
- Development of new functionality;
- Integration of third-party services;
- CRUD from UI to database (Mongo, SQL).

CJSC ADVIN SMART FACTORY, 2021 - 2022

FRONT-END DEVELOPER (REACT / REDUX)

- Creating of universal components;
- Creating login forms and universal models;
- Application architecture organization (UI, BLL, DAL);
- -Github collaboration experience.

CJSC KATEK, 2017 - 2021 rr.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER, 2020-2021

- Creating of universal components:
- Creating login forms and universal models;

TESTING ENGINEER, 2017-2020

- Creating configurations for the programmable logic controllers;
- Working with databases (MySQL);
- Testing programmable logic controller configurations;
- Conducting electrical tests:
- Management of subordinate personnel.